[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Were you surprised in the end that she fell on her sword today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "You didn't believe it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "I didn't believe it because here you had an attack with rocket-propelled hand grenades, mortars, very well executed, very well prepared.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Don't you -- don't you exercise some intelligence about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "ORGAN: Here's what she said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "What was her job that day, Rudy, to be fair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Common sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rudy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "But do you think she lied?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "I don't know that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Is that a fair criticism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Also fair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Would you therefore object to her becoming secretary of state personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Personally I don't believe she would serve the country well in that capacity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Would I support it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", ":", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I think our -- some people in our military are going to have a very hard time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "If you were President Obama then, who would you go for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Well, what I'm saying is I'm not President Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Are you looking at this as a pre-Christmas done deal, Rudy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "I think so, because it seems so obvious that you have to do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rudy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "What is your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "I agree there should be a sensible debate about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Norway"]}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "I didn't -- I didn't agree, I didn't agree that it necessarily should result in immediate gun control because I look at the murder that took place in Norway or in Finland where, what, 79 people were killed without a gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", ",", "WP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Norway.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Norway", "Finland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "If he doesn't get the AR-15, he'll go get a handgun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "-- running a country with so many guns to try and make it harder?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "There's no question about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret Hoover"]}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Let me start with you, Margaret Hoover.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Are they right to be pleased about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "I don't know for them if it's as much personally about her or if it's about Benghazi.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "That's not great for a progressive president like Barack Obama, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Yes -- no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "What's it like to be Warren Buffett's son?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Well, first, I'm afraid you know more about me than I know, so that's my first concern.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "How long was the period?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Three years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "I mean, did he ever even nearly succumb to the pressure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Oh, no, it was a deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Was there a formal handshake, a contract?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Yes -- no, the handshake was it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "That's it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Has your dad always been a handshake man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Are you all like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "And you're all the same?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "What did work over the years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Well, I think the things that have worked -- I'm not sure exactly specifically what you're after.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Would you be happy to pay more tax?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "I don't think you have to pay more tax.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Final question, what on Earth do you buy Warren Buffett for Christmas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Now you've put me on the spot.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Do you go small?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "You go with any idea you have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What did you get him last year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "I bet he's never happier, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "No, he loves it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "How difficult has it been for you, Damien?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "It was incredibly difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Damien"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "What else?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "I've actually gained 60 pounds in the past year that I was out, because now I have adequate nutrition and decent exercise, things like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "And how do you think he's been coping?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "First of all, it's amazing to have him out here with us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "What do you think have been the hardest things for Damien to deal with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "It's the little things, like going to the bank and filling out a deposit slip or going through security at the airport.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Damien"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "What was it that appealed to you from a documentary maker pointing of view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Well, the story had so many twists and turns.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Of course the lottery turned out to be a shameful farce, didn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "And what you didn't hear was actually that that knife was actually thrown in the lake a year before the murders even happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "When you hear that, given your knowledge and experience of Death Row, given what we now know about DNA and the way it's been exonerating many people on Death Row, what do you think of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "It's absolutely nightmarish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "How many people did you meet or encounter on Death Row who you basically believe may have been innocent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I would say in the time I was there, probably three others.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "Would DNA evidence, had it been around when you were arrested, have cleared you from the start?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "CHOLS: I don't know, because they wanted to convict us so badly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", ":", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "What the significant of those?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "It's sort of -- really what it comes down to, it helps me deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "What are the ones on your knuckles?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "These are runes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "How important to you and powerful to you has it been to have Lorri's unequivocal backing and support through all of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "I could not have survived in prison or out of prison without her.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lorri"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "Where did you go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "He wanted to take me to the desert to see the wild flowers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "You turned down Marlon Brando?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlon Brando"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "How did he take rejection?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "It was fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]